Are you prepared to testify under oath here today that
covid-19 is a bioweapon? Yes, I am.
Bringing truth, delighted, unbiased and nonpartisan
factually founded reporting worldwide.
Dr. Fleming, we've asked you to come testify about whether
Covid-19 and related vaccines are a deliberate bioweapon
attack on the United States.
Adam Court Reporter can you please identify yourself for
the record? My name is Karen Usher.
Texas. CSR number 5536.
Thank you.
Can you please swear in the witness? Dr.
Fleming, will you raise your right hand? Do you swear the
testimony you give today will be the truth, the whole
truth, and nothing but the truth will help you God? I do.
Dr. Fleming, do you consent to this testimony being used in
any appropriate proceeding? Yes, I do.
First, I'd like to cover some of your qualifications.
You have an impressive 90 page resume.
I'm not going to go through that.
But very briefly, are you a medical doctor? Yes, I am.
So therefore you have an MD degree, as it's known.
I do, yes.
And what is your area of specialty? Nuclear cardiology.
Cardiology and internal medicine.
And do you also belong to professional medical
associations? Yes, I do.
Are you a fellow of the American College of Physicians? Yes.
And are you a fellow of the American Society of Internal
Medicine? Yes.
And you also hold a PhD.
Yes, I do.
And in what field is this? Physics. And you also have a law degree,
otherwise known as a JD.
I do.
And are you an inventor in the medical field? Yes.
And very briefly, can you explain the type of medical
inventions that you've invented? The ability to image the
body and determine what types of disease processes are
going on by looking at metabolism and blood flow.
Do you hold patents for your inventions? Yes, I do.
Is it fair to say you're familiar with the world of medical
patents? Yes.
You have the ability to read and interpret medical patents?
Yes, I do.
And are you also an author of professional papers? Yes, sir.
And approximately how many? Somewhere between 4 and 500.
And do you also serve on the editorial board of
professional journals? On editorial boards and review
boards for the journals.
And briefly, what does a reviewer in a professional journal
do? The obligation is when somebody submits a paper for
publication, for reviewers to take a look at that material,
to determine if it's scientifically valid, to determine if
it makes a difference in the field, and to make
recommendations back to the editorial board about whether
the papers should be accepted or revised or rejected for
publication.
Are you prepared to testify under oath here today that
Covid-19 is a bioweapon? Yes, I am.
You wrote a book posing the question, Is COVID-19 a
bioweapon? Correct? Correct.
The function of the book was to provide information that
the general public could look at and also to provide
evidence for the legal system and the medical system to
understand the gain of function research that has been
carried out over a couple of decades.
To show where the money came from.
To show what papers were published showing what types of
gain of function research occurred.
And to show the patents to clearly lay out two decades
worth of work that's been conducted,
funded primarily by the United States.
Although other countries have been involved.
And to show how there's no evidence that SARS-CoV2
The virus that causes Covid-19.
No evidence to show that it's naturally occurring.
No animal model for it.
And to show the type of research that's been done with
coronaviruses funded by the US.
Supported by NIAID NIH Department of Defense money that
went to Peter Daszak at Eco Health, to  Ralph Baric at the
University of North Carolina, to Shi Zhengli at the Wuhan Institute of virology,
and there are several other
universities around the country, including in the state of Texas
Did you also look at the genetic code of the SARS-CoV2
virus and especially the spike protein? We did,
as well as Professor Luke Montaignier, who is the gentleman who
discovered the HIV virus, and several other individuals
that we note in the book.
And based on that review of the genetic code that informs
your conclusion that this is a bio weapon, right.
So the Biological Weapons Convention Treaty states that any
adjustment or modification of a biological agent like this
virus that doesn't provide a benefit for mankind is a
biological weapon.
These particular changes in this virus.
Including the PRRA insert, which are amino acids that were inserted.
That are very critical for the pure and cleavage site for
this virus to infect. The insertion sites that were made
with HIV and Simian or ape-like HIV equivalent viruses.
The prion like domain at the top of the spike protein.
As well as the HIV Glycoprotein 120 insert that Shi Zhengli
put in early on.
That's critical for the attachment of this virus to cells.
All of which are not naturally occurring.
So to be clear, the SARS-CoV2 virus, otherwise known as
Covid-19, and especially its spiked protein, is not
something that's simply involved on its own in nature.
We've looked at all the different coronaviruses that exist
on the planet.
None of them have the PRRA insert, none of them have this
tremendous amount of HIV insert.
None of them have a regional binding domain that is a prion-like
binding domain, which means that where it attaches to
the cells, it's a prion-like domain.
And prions are things that are abnormal proteins that cause
other proteins to become abnormally folded.
So to be clear, genetic changes were made to the spike
protein in a lab to create what is known as the COVID-19.
Correct? That's what all the data shows.
Your book references research in 2010 by Shi Zhang Li, who
is often called the Bat Lady.
Was that research designed to determine how to increase the spike protein binding capacity to the human S2 receptor.
So that was her goal of that research, was to
increase the ability of the virus to infect human cells.
Now, interestingly, I think in this published research,
they discovered that the naturally occurring spike protein
from horseshoe bats was unable to bind to the human S2
receptors. Right? That's exactly right.
So as of 2010, scientists, including Shi Zhengli and Wuhan
China, knew that naturally occurring horseshoe back
coronavirus spike proteins could not infect humans.
That's right.
Based on your testimony, it sounds like you discovered at
least two man made inserts into the SARS-CoV2 spike
protein genetic code that prove it was produced in a lab.
Right. The research papers that Shi Zhengli and Baric
and others published, they were very clear and somewhat
proud of the fact that they've been able to modify the
virus and to insert changes into it that made it more
effective and potentially more dangerous.
There's some laboratory mechanism where they're able to
take genetic code from elsewhere and put it into a virus.
Right. So you can actually build anything if you know what
the structures are.
It's like building a car if you know what the parts are,
you simply put it together.
Many of the research studies that we have pointed out, they
took bits and pieces of one virus, combined it with bits
and pieces of another virus.
If you go and look at those papers, you'll also find that
they were very specific by inserting five nucleotide base
pairs in there.
So they simply switched the base pairs, and that will result in a different amino acid being added in a different protein.
Let's talk about the first insert that you found
in the SARS-CoV2 virus that led you to conclude that it
was a man made bioweapon.
The first one I think you referred to as the furin cleavage
PRRA insert.
Correct? That's correct.
Can you explain briefly what that is? Okay, so that's four
amino acids that were put in when this virus attaches.
And I know this is long and complicated because a lot of
people have heard of S2, which is one of the
receptors, but it's a multi step process.
The HIV Glycoprotein 120 insert, which was the second one
we talked about, is required to attach to what's called a
cyanic acid receptor raft that stabilizes it and puts it in position.
The virus then comes into contact with the H2
receptor that then undergoes a change with something called
a TMPRSS-2 receptor, which is critical to understanding
because that begins the process of bringing that virus into
the cell.
It then has to undergo furin cleavage at the Furin cleavage
site. And that's the PRRA, which makes it particularly
infective for human cells.
And then it comes across also something known as neuropilin-1 receptor, which is found in the brain.
How did you discover that this PRRA cleavage insert had
been made to SARS-CoV2.
All you have to do is the nucleotide base sequencing, which
is how we know all the variants occur.
And when you do that, you find this PRRA insert.
Now, this genetic code for the furin cleavage insert, the
PRRA, is that found in any other coronavirus in nature?
None. It's not found in any other coronavirus that exists
in the wild.
Right. There's absolutely no other coronavirus that has
this PRRA insert.
That's twelve nucleotide bases.
Not a single base like sickle cell, but twelve specific
nucleotide bases to provide for four amino acids that very
specifically is connected with the furin cleavage site
which the US government owns the patent on.
So the fact that this insert and this genetic sequence for
this insert is not found in any other coronavirus in
nature, what does that tell you?
Well, since mutations occur one nucleotide base at a time, you would have to come
up with some phenomenal explanation for why twelve
nucleotide bases suddenly inserted themselves into a virus
that none of it the other viruses in that category have.
The original premise that was put forward and actually
published in The Lancet was that this was a naturally
occurring virus with an animal host that got transmitted to people.
But yet there's not been a single animal model
found with this.
Neither has there been a single coronavirus that has this
PRRA insert.
You mentioned the second insert, an HIV Glycoprotein.
Right. So are you saying that sections of the genetic code
for HIV were inserted into the SARS-CoV2 virus? Yes.
Shi Zhengli published this early on, many years ago, where
she was very proud of the fact that she did this.
She used an HIV pseudovirus to do it.
And we also know that HIV Glycoprotein 120 is a prion.
So this is the HIV that became famous in the 1980s and 1990s.
That HIV?
Right. And somebody took pieces of the genetic code of HIV
and put it into SARS-CoV2.
That's what Shi Zhengli admitted to in publications that
she had.
Yes. Were you able to discover why that was done? According
to papers that she published, it was to increase the
infectivity to see if she could make it more effective.
But it's even clearer that what she was going for was the
development of a prion disease.
Because where everybody is kind of coming up to speed with
a virus and how challenging it can be to deal with, what's
even more challenging to deal with are prions.
Because prion diseases are relatively new in our
understanding, for treatment, and they cause permanent
damage unless they can be reversed.
And so the development of a prion, putting HIV Glycoprotein
120 in there, attaching to the salic acid receptor,
there's nothing about that  is advantageous for people.
And the ability to produce prion diseases is quite a
weapon. And how lethal are prion diseases? People die from
prion diseases.
This process of inserting these amino acids to increase the
infectivity is that gain of function, right. So gain of
function is anything that you do that changes a naturally
occurring biological agent like this virus.
The premise of gain of function really has a good premise
behind it.
The original idea being that if you could stay a step ahead
of a potential infectious agent, say a coronavirus, if you
could say just a step ahead, you could do a good job of
providing treatments for people and knowing when and where
it was going to spread.
This isn't a step ahead.
This isn't a single nucleotide base.
This is a spike protein that has an HIV Glycoprotein 120
insert into it.
This is a spike protein that has four amino acids to make a
pure and cleavage site the PRRA insert.
This is a spike protein that has multiple others, According to Luke Montagnier, HIV and SIV inserts.
This is not something that evolutionarily evolved.
The evolution of something with this many changes would
take hundreds or thousands of years.
This is not staying a step ahead of it and making this
provided no advantage for human beings, which makes it a
Biological Weapons Convention treaty violation.
This is playing up.
To your knowledge, has anyone been able to disprove or
refute the fact that there are artificial man made
insertions into the SARS-CoV2 virus? Actually, there's
been no dispute of that except for the statement that it's
naturally occurring.
And then when you say, well, where's the scientific
evidence that it's naturally occurring? There's no follow
up to that.
So that for people that are claiming that this is a
scientific discussion, I would encourage them to stay with
the fact that this is a scientific discussion.
There's no science to show that any other coronavirus on
the planet has these inserts.
There's no science to show that there's a natural reservoir
and animal for this virus to occur.
In fact, the science points to the fact with over 99%
probability, which is what we're dealing with, until
somebody comes up and confesses that this is not naturally occuring.
In your mind, is there any doubt that without
this gain of function manipulation of the SARS-CoV2
spike protein, there would have been no pandemic
we wouldn't have had this, had this virus not been released.
Have any of these folks, Daszak, Baric, Shi Zhengli, Fauci
explained what that beneficial alleged effect is?
Well, up until now, it seems like most of their conversation has
been we didn't do anything like that, even though the data
is now showing it.
But as we've learned over the last couple of months, the
National Institutes of Health and National Institutes of
Allergies and Infectious Disease have now admitted that
they needed to.
But it's nice for them to admit that a gain of functional
research was funded for by the US.
And that Fauci statements that they weren't involved in
gain of function research was not correct.
Dr. Faucie testified under oath to Congress, under
questioning by Senator Rand Paul that the NIH and NIAID had
not funded gain a function research.
Was that statement truthful? Well, as we've shown and as
we've talked about, that was a lie.
And that lie can be proven by publicly available documents.
Dr. Fauci denied under oath that they provided any gain of
functional research just despite the fact that we have a
long track record of gain of function research.
In fact, that gain of function research even occurred
during the time that it would shut down during the Clinton
administration due to concern by scientists like myself
that saw problems with infections getting out from gain of
function research.
That money still got funneled around primarily through
Peter Dezak, whom it got funneled out to Baric and Shi Zhengli and other sources.
And they're denying that they're connected with each other
just completely goes in the face their
publications, published papers where both of their names,
Baris and Shi Zhengli around there.
You can find the publications that show NIH funding.
This was not a well hidden secret.
NIH has now come out since with a statement admitting that
they have provided gain of function research.
And part of this gain of function was designed to make that
coronavirus spike proteins infectious to humans when they
were not before.
It's very clear from the research grants that were paid for by the United States from the published papers
that Shi Zheng Li and the others have published by the pattens have been published that they
specifically set out to increase and
made possible the ability of these viruses to infect.
Particularly with the HKU-4 and the HIV pseudovirus
glycoprotein -120 inserts that Shi Zhengli and the others were involved with.
That they intentionally sought to make this more infectious
and, in fact, Accomplished it.
And who were the main players in these genetic engineering experiments?
Well, the primary ones that we know of are
Peter Desak at Eco Health, Ralph Baric at the University
of North Carolina, and Shi Zhengli at the Wuan Institute
of Virology.
But we know that there's been other individuals involved.
We know that other universities, including here in Texas
how are you able to uncover this gain of function research and who funded it?
There were a lot of very interesting
sources that were coming forth suggesting places to look.
But basically what I did is what any researcher does when
they ask a question, which is if you know what question to
ask, you can get a wealth of information if somebody has it
out there.
So I began querying the federal funding sources
specifically looking at Eco Health and gain of function research.
And that allowed me to run down the actual grant numbers.
So what we have in the book, you don't have to
take my word for it, is the actual grant numbers, how much
monies there were, whether it came from the Department of Defense, which, by the way, paid for more than half of this.
Did you discover there were attempts to cover up the
funding of this gain of function research?
Yeah, there were a lot of attempts, not very good ones, as far as I'm
concerned, but including the Lancet letter where Dezak and
so many others got together and then published that 'this
was obviously a naturally occurring virus' doing everything
imaginable to skew the scientific medical literature,
to get people to not consider the possibility of it being a
gain of function laboriented bioweapons.
And did this research violate any treaties or laws? The
Biological Weapons Convention treaty is very specific.
It states that any bacterial agent, in this case a virus
that does not have a benefit for humanity is a violation of
the Biological Weapons Convention Treaty.
And it's important to note that this is a treaty that the
United States has signed and ratified.
Article Six of the US.
Constitution states that treaties are the supreme law of
the land.
The signing and ratification of the Biological Weapons
Convention treaty.
The signing and ratification of the International Covenant
on Civil and Political Rights.
The United States participating in the Nuremberg Trials of 1947
to establish the Nuremberg Code and how patients would be
treated, the Declaration of Helsinki that the US.
Has committed to for research patients.
The American Medical Association Code of Ethics on Informed
Consent, that 'anybody violating these have already
demonstrated that they not only are interested in providing
informed consent and patient rights, but if they're
violating a treaty, they have violated the US. Constitution.
And anybody who has taken an oath of office,
anybody who has stood there and sworn to uphold and defend
the Constitution of the United States, who then ignores
these treaties,  funds violation of
these treaties, as was done in this instance,
who refuses to allow patients to have informed consent, the
International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights.
If you've done that, you have violated the US. Constitution.
And if you've taken an oath to uphold
defend the Constitution, then you have committed treason.
When you reach the conclusion that SARS-CoV2 was a
bioweapon released on the planet, what was your reaction?
Uncomfortable and disappointed.
These individuals have presented nothing to suggest that
this type of research was something that they thought was
for the benefit of humanity.
And considering the funding sources...
If you look at the Emergency Use Authorization documents,
the documents submitted to the FDA, you have to ask
yourself two questions, and the data is right in the EUA documents.
The first question is, how many people get sick?
And that's this number that we talk about, vaccine
efficacy, how many people get sick if they're vaccinated
versus how many people get sick if they weren't vaccinated?
So that's a vaccine efficacy number.
But if you ask the question, Why are people getting
vaccinated? That's not why they're getting vaccinated.
They're getting vaccinated so they don't get sick.
And that's called an absolute risk reduction.
And if you go to the EUA documents, for Pfizer Moderna Johnson
and the three that are EUA approved in the US.
And you asked that fundamental question, how many people do
not get sick for pfizer that using their data? There is no
statistically significant reduction in COVID cases for
vaccinated people versus unvaccinated.
If you look at Moderna, the same thing, no statistical
reduction in Covid cases for the vaccinated versus the
unvaccinated. Jansson did a little bit more complex.
They looked at results at two weeks, 14 days after their
injection, and 28 days or four weeks.
Now, if you look at their data at two weeks after the
injection, there is a statistical reduction in the number
of COVID cases.
If you carry that out two more weeks, which they did, that
difference is gone.
So if you want to vaccinate people, I guess every two
weeks, go for it.
It doesn't prevent you from getting infected.
Statistically it didn't reduce the number of COVID cases or deaths, and
it doesn't prevent you from transmitting it.
And that's what we're seeing right now.
No virus comes in just one flavor, if you will.
Just like if you look around a room, you'll see a whole
bunch of people and they're all variants, but they're all
very much human, right? So SARS-CoV2 didn't just come as
WUHAN-HU1
It had the alpha and the beta and the gamma and the lambda
and the delta and all the other variants, all the different changes.
And what we've done in the past is we've taken and
made vaccines by taking all of the parts of a virus with
all of the variants and weakening it, and then injecting that into people,
so that if you saw another version of it
or other parts of it, you would have an immune response to it.
What we did with these vaccines is we very specifically
said, let's just look at the spike protein of the original one,
the one called WUHAN-HU1, and let's make that
genetic code and turn the human cells into a manufacturing
plant to make those spiked proteins.
What did that do? But the people who got vaccinated, many of them who did it because they were worried about other people.
So understanding that these people were well
intentioned, they were afraid, they were fearful.
They didn't want somebody else to get sick because of them.
They didn't want other family members to become sick.
They didn't want the man or the woman down the street who
had cancer or heart disease to become sick.
So as good citizens, they were told, you need to do this
and it will make a difference, but the vaccines don't
prevent you from getting infected or spreading it.
So by using this approach, we injected this mRNA and DNA
into people for just one type of spike protein,
not the rest of the virus, not the nucleic capsid, which turns out
to be what humans make the best immune response to, not the
envelope, not the membrane, and not the other types of
spike protein. One type!
And so what we see is people getting vaccinated with it.
And if you track what's happened, not only in the United
States, but around the world as these vaccines have been
used, fewer and fewer people have gotten infected with the
WUHAN-HU1.
Or if they've gotten infected, they were ready for it, but
they weren't ready for the other variants.
The alpha, the beta, the gamma, the delta, the mu, the now
Omicron, as people like to call it, what I call it 21K.
But Omicron is now the term for it.
Those, they didn't have an immune response too, so they
responded to it rapidly.
And then when they spread the virus to other people, they
spread the ones that weren't attacked because the immune
system wasn't ready for it.
So we've done a great job of pressure selecting out this
virus to the variants so that we're spreading and shifting it.
And now the spike protein of Omicron is so much
different than even delta or alpha or WUHAN-HU1 that the ability
of our immune system to respond to that isn't there.
And we're seeing more and more people with this variant
coming down with symptoms and spreading it to other people.
When you ask to have the vaccines done a good job of
reducing this, all you have to do is look at the science.
All you have to do is look at the numbers.
Israel vaccinated the vast majority of its country with the
Pfizer and oederna vaccines, and their cases of delta
escalated right off the chart as a result of it.
They simply did pressure selection.
In the United States, we've done the same thing where we're
seeing the Omicron variants and the Delta variants being
pressure selected out by this vaccine program.
This has not helped reduce it.
It simply shifted the variants and persisted the problem
and stressed people and made people afraid.
In this case, if you look at the data, the difference
between vaccinated and unvaccinated on an absolute risk
reduction standard was statistically insignificant.
The absolute risk reduction is somewhere between 0.8 and
1.3%. And that was known by the FDA and the drug
manufacturers before these vaccines were rolled out.
What bothers me, I watched these FDA meetings for the EUA,
and none of the people on the panel raised the question,
what's the absolute risk reduction, which is the goal of
actually vaccinating people? I watched the FDA meetings for
the booster shots, and I don't remember whether it was
Pfizer or Moderna.
I want to say it was Moderna, but I won't swear to it.
The head of their vaccine project said that T cell response
was unimportant.
Well, T cell response is critical because you have T cells
and B cells, and it just refers to where they come from.
But the T cell response, it's called innate immunity, is
critical. And it's the first thing that happens to people,
the B cells or antibody responses occurs several days
later. But for the antibody response to occur, the T cells
have to be working.
And we know from published data and I provided documents on
this that the Pfizer Moderna vaccines suppress the T cell
response in people that get the vaccine.
Not only does the count of those cells go down, but the
chemicals that they produce, interferon which simply
means it interferes with the production of viruses.
And what's called T helper two cells, which are a type of T
cell that's critical to help make the right antibody
response. All of that is suppressed in individuals who get
these vaccines.
Listening to people tell me that they're 'Mr science'. Or Big
Pharma saying that it's 'all about the science' or anybody
else saying it's 'all about the science',
I'm seeing a tremendous lack of actual science integrity and
interrogation of the science.
Because when you go into the documents, the EUA
documents and you do the science, you do the
interrogation of the data to see if it's really different,
you discover it's not.
The data is very clear.
The science is very clear.
The vaccines have not done anything to reduce COVID cases
or deaths.
Just a fundamental question.
If you understand that the spike protein is a gain of
function bioweapon, why would you then replicate that
same genetic sequence and put it in a vaccine?
I think most people are under the impression that you get an injection
in your muscle, that it stays in your muscle.
Right? Except that's not what happens.
The studies are very clear.
The lip nanoparticle influenza vaccine made by moderna
spread to the brain,
the bone marrow, the liver, the spleen, the heart, kidneys,
the intestine, every part of the animal's body. It doesn't stay
at the site of injection.
These things aren't being directly injected into your
cells. They're being injected into muscle which has fluid
around the cells that drains out to the rest of your body
and gets into your bloodstream where it can have some very
serious consequences.
Some of the research that we've recently done has looked at
the Pfizer Moderna and Jansen vaccines and what happens
when they are introduced into human blood.
Now, is the introduction of the spike protein into the body
through these so called vaccines functionally different
than the introduction of those spike proteins through the SARS-CoV2 virus?
When people spread infections back and
forth, they spread hundreds of thousands or if you want to
be generous, 10,000 virus particles by coughing or sneezing
on somebody.
And so that's the amount that you would get exposed to.
And that's why back in 2020 we saw so many people with the
comorbidities because they already had diseases where there
was inflammation and blood clotting going on
With the vaccines, those numbers are significantly different.
We're not talking about thousands or tens of thousands.
We're talking about billions in these vaccines.
Billions of spiked proteins? Billions of genetic sequences
to make spike proteins.
For Pfizer Moderna  it's 131 Billion. For Jansen and AstraZeneca it's 50 billion.
And the other thing is that a virus to get into your cell
has to find that S2  receptor that we talked about.
These vaccines don't.
The lipid nanoparticles simply merge with your cell
membrane. They don't have to look for any S2 receptors to
get in.
They simply merge with it and release all that genetic sequence.
What we're seeing with vaccinated individuals
are healthy people reacting.
Why? Because they're not getting exposed to 1000 or 10,000
virus particles from somebody else who coughed or sneezed
on them which shouldn't have coughed or sneezed on them. Right?
They're getting billions.
And if they have a functioning healthy body, their immune
system is looking at that and saying, wow, we have just
been massively infected.
And they mount an immune response.
That immune response has inflammation and blood clotting.
You release chemicals to kill the cells that are infected.
That's why you get a runny nose that's that fluid being
released and blood clotting to wall off the invader so that
it can't get out, number one.
And number two, it can't get nutrients, and so it dies.
So that inflammation, blood clotting is what your body
should do, except you don't get infected with billions of
these viruses.
So healthy people are reacting to something that looks like
a nuclear bomb went off in their body and they're reacting
to it, producing a lot of inflammation, a lot of blood
clotting, and a lot of very adverse events.
And what we're seeing with all the people with adverse
events are all the people that are healthy, younger,
responding to what appears to be an overwhelming infection
in their body with all the spike proteins.
And we're seeing inflammation and blood clotting.
And you've seen it with strokes and seizures and heart
disease and miscarriages and death that we've never seen
before in the history of mankind for vaccines that have
been made.
I remember in the 70s, mainstream media 60 Minutes did a
documentary showing exposing the lies by Big Pharma and the
FDA on the swine flu vaccine.
And at 25 deaths, we decided that something needed to be
done. So it really doesn't matter to me whether it's been
15,000 deaths or 150,000 deaths.
If in 1976, 25 deaths was enough to cause people to say,
we need to investigate this, and in 2020, 15,000
deaths isn't enough, we have a problem.
Well, have you seen any evidence that Pfizer
Johnson and Johnson Moderna did animal studies before they
went to the FDA for emergency use authorization?
I have not. And I have to tell you that all of these call for
animal models to be done before you do it in the human so
that you know what would happen.
And I've done animal research for many decades of my life,
and there's a reason for doing it.
It's because you don't experiment on people unless you're Nazis.
And if I understand it correctly, the CDC VAERS
reporting system is showing more deaths and injuries from
COVID-19 vaccines than all other vaccines combined for the
last 30 years.
It is. Independent of whether you believe those numbers or
not. You think they're 1% or 10%, whether you should put 10
or two zeros behind the numbers.
Here are some interesting things about this reporting
system. As a physician, I've tried to call in to the
VAERS reporting system and I get a recording that gives
me another telephone number to go to.
When I call that number, it gives me a recording and no
place to leave a message.
I have colleagues who have tried to enter it in on the
computer system and it keeps bouncing back.
Now, if you come into a hospital or doctor's office and you
have an adverse event to measles, mumps and Rubella
vaccines, there's a code to enter into that and it goes
into the computer.
If you have an adverse event to diphtheria tetanus vaccine,
there's a code for that. That goes into the computer and
that will be tracked through history.
These things are called computerized procedural terminology
CPT codes.
There is no CPT code to enter into a computer system for an
adverse event to any of these SARS-CoV2 vaccines.
Even though this is part of a clinical trial and therefore
they have a legal obligation to track adverse events, there
is no universal code for physicians to code in an adverse
event? That's right.
Have you ever seen that before? It's the first time.
So these are vaccines that, as I understand it, the ones
that are available are still part of a clinical trial that
lasts until 2023, correct? That's what it shows, yes, on
the national clinical trial site.
And when you're doing a clinical trial, one of the most
important things you need to do is accurately track adverse events,I would assume.
We're going to look back on this.
We're going to look not too distance in the future.
We're going to look back on 2020 and 2021, 2021 in particular and say how
many people really had an adverse event to these vaccines.
Now, have you seen any animal studies that have been
produced or released by any of the current vaccine
manufacturers before emergency use authorization?
I haven't seen any animal studies by those corporations before or
after they've come out.
The only animal studies that have been done are by
independent scientists who have been asking the questions
that these companies should have been asking, which is what
are the consequences in animals to these vaccines?
What has that research uncovered? The research done by independent
researchers have shown that there is damage to the brains
and other body organs caused by these viruses and these
vaccines that are called prion diseases.
So you can have mad cow disease in the brain or Alzheimer's
in the brain or amyloid disease in the heart, which is
another type of prion disease.
But the studies done by people doing the research on the
animals have been very clear and very consistent.
Prion diseases, inflammation and blood clotting or thrombotic
diseases, and real concerns about miscarriages and other
health problems and deaths.
None of this has been done by Pfizer, Moderna, Jensen or
the other companies.
This animal research could have been done before the
Emergency Use Authorization, but we have no record that it
was ever done or reported.
This animal research should have been done.
It violates every Treaty and Code that we've ever had as
human beings.
There was one instance in time that animal research was
abandoned by doing it on people first.
And we prosecuted those people in 1947 at the Nuremberg Trials.
One of the questions that we had was what happens
if the vaccine gets into your blood? We've looked at
Pfizer, Moderna, and Janssen, all three, and we have looked
at the effect that those vaccines have on the blood, and
it's almost immediate.
What we're going to look at are just three examples of
slides that we took from seven different patients and the
three different vaccines where we put samples of blood on a
microscope slide and looked at them under the microscope.
And what you're going to see here in the first image,
you're going to see the Pfizer vaccine that was added to
the blood.
And you're going to see the nice red color of Rythrocytes,
or red blood cells.
That's because they're able to carry oxygen from the lungs
to the body.
And what you're going to see next to them are a lot of gray
cells. These are still what's called red blood cells,
although they're no longer red because they are no longer
able to carry oxygen.
And since there's plenty of oxygen already in the air, what
we're seeing is an inability for the hemoglobin in those
cells to bind oxygen.
And they stay this way.
After many minutes of watching them, they didn't turn back
or even begin to turn back.
And then the second slide you're going to look at, we're
going to see the exact same thing in another patient.
This is Medorna once it's been added and you see the same phenomenon.
And then finally, the third cell is the Janssen
vaccine, showing the exact same phenomenon with a loss of
the ability of the hemoglobin to hold oxygen as shown by
gray cells next to the bright red cells that are still functioning,
that haven't been damaged by the vaccine.
If we look at these slides, what we're seeing is that when
you added the vaccine to the red blood cells, the red
coloration goes away.
The red coloration goes away, and it stays away.
And it's not a matter of adding just a liquid to it because
we also looked at blood when we added normal Saline to it,
and it dilutes it out a little bit, but it doesn't take the
red color away.
All three of these vaccines, when we added them to the
blood, the red color to the blood cells goes away,
which means the hemoglobin is no longer able to carry oxygen.
So that could be due to a couple of things.
There's no oxygen to carry.
Well, it's open to the atmosphere, so there's plenty of
oxygen. So it means the hemoglobin molecule has been
damaged or the membrane of the red blood cell has been damaged.
But sickle cell anemia is a damaged, altered blood
cell and it has no difficulty being a red blood cell.
So something's happened to the hemoglobin molecule and it
doesn't reverse.
We've watched the blood for many minutes.
It doesn't reverse.
The other thing we saw is that the blood begins to clump
together and it's not a matter of time because we watched
regular blood of the same individuals with normal saline
added to it and their blood didn't clump.
So it's not a time phenomenon.
It's not because they were drawn up in tubes that had
solutions in them that affected the red blood cells,
because this blood was drawn directly from the patients,
wasn't put in any tubes with any other material in it that
could interfere with it.
So this is a phenomenon of the vaccines get added.
Where the vaccines touch the red blood cells, the red blood
cells turn pale.
They're no longer red.
The important thing is not only the oxygen carrying
capacity, but the fact that that same hemoglobin that picks
up oxygen from your lungs and takes it to your body when
it's in your body, takes the carbon dioxide, the waste
product, out the acid, and takes it back to your lungs.
Well, if the hemoglobin has been damaged so it can't carry
oxygen, that same damage exists and it's unlikely that it's
going to even be able to carry the carbon dioxide out,
although carrying the oxygen is kind of a big deal for red
blood cells.
And what would be the consequences of having this depletion
of the oxygen carrying capacity of the blood cells?
Well, none of those red blood cells can carry any oxygen to your
body. The real question is how much of that is going on in
any individual.
And no amount of this vaccine, of any of these vaccines
should have damaging effect on red blood cells.
Again, this is a tissue level thing.
This is early on stuff.
This is like the animal studies.
If you're going to be looking at doing something, giving a
drug to a patient, you need to know that the drug will work
and you need to know what consequences there may be.
Seriously, this is an easy project to do.
You take the vaccines, you take human blood, you add it to
it, and if anybody can prove to me that what we saw
repeatedly is wrong, hey, go for it, prove me wrong.
But you're not going to because the beautiful thing about
science is that we've conducted this in more than one site
on the planet, and seven different people with all three
vaccines, they all had the same devastating effect to the blood.
Do you have a working theory or hypothesis as to why
these vaccines are causing this blood cell discoloration
and clumping? Yeah, I actually do.
We've known for a long period of time that RNA or DNA, when
it's outside of a cell, is a prion.
Human red blood cells are the only cells in the human body
that don't have a nucleus and they don't have ribosomes.
All they have is hemoglobin to carry oxygen and carbon
dioxide. So red blood cells can't do anything with genetic
code that's entered into it.
Now, the lipid nanoparticles would simply merge with the
red blood cells.
If the red blood cells behave like any other part of the
body does, that's outside of a cell that doesn't have a
nucleus or ribosomes, when RNA or DNA comes into contact
with it, it acts like a prion and changes the protein structure.
Hemoglobin is a protein.
So what it looks to us like is happening is these vaccines
are releasing the RNA or the DNA from the vaccine into the
red blood cells, having a prime effect on the hemoglobin molecule,
permanently changing the hemoglobin molecule so
that it no longer has the same shape or configuration, so I
can't find oxygen, and it won't be able to pick up carbon
dioxide.
Dr. Fleming, are the vaccines reprogramming the innate immune system?
What we have seen is that two of the critical steps
for your immune system the production of something called interferon,
which means it interferes with the replication
of the virus, and T helper 2 cells, which are critical
for helping to make antibodies, those are all suppressed.
Now, T helper 2 cells, I know, is a term people haven't
heard. It's a type of T cell.
It helps, and it's number two in the sequence.
It has three components that actually need to match up with
the B cells that make antibodies.
Only when all three of those match up does a signal get
sent to your antibody system, what's called the adaptive
humoral antibody system, to make antibodies of a specific
type targeting a specific infection, and to keep memory
cells for that.
Now, in the absence of those T help 2 cells being
produced like they should, that system, even though it
exists, is going to be blunted.
Based on all of this, would somebody be totally off base if
they believe these vaccines were, in and of themselves, a bioweapon?
Well, the fact that the spike protein is a gain
of function developed virus, which, by definition, is a bioweapon,
replicating that same genetic sequence and
putting it into a vaccine, it doesn't matter how you get it
into the human body.
It's still a bioweapon.
Most alarmingly for the children right now, when you have
people at an FDA meeting making a statement that we need to
vaccinate the children, but we won't know what happens to
them until we vaccinate them.
That's the experimental phase of a research project.
And as of 1947, I thought that we had officially, although
it's very clear from the Tuskegee Airmen and other studies
that have been done, paid for by the US. Government,
that it seems that our leaders don't have a
problem experimenting on our elderly, on our police
officers, on our first responders, on our doctors and nurses,
on our general public, and now apparently don't
have a problem experimenting on our children.
So if you were advising, for example, the Texas Health
Commissioner on how to fight this attack, what would you recommend?
Well, it goes back to one of the statements I
made earlier.
When you're doing something in medicine or science of any
sort and there's a bad outcome, you quit doing it.
One of my medical students came up to me, said, Dr.
Fleminng, it didn't work the last few times.
We gave this medication to somebody, and they had a really
bad outcome, but I want to try it again, because maybe
it'll work this time.
I'd probably kick them off the rotation.
We don't keep repeating the things that caused the problem.
All the evidence shows there's no statistical benefit to
using these vaccines.
The mass vaccination has caused pressure selection of these
variants. It has produced significant adverse effects in
the people it's been given to.
The FDA has admitted during its EUA documents for children
that we won't know what it does to our children until we
experiment on our children.
It's very clear these vaccines have done nothing to solve
the problem.
They need to be stopped.
The companies need to be held legally accountable.
The questions about why all these Codes and Treaties that
we claim that we honor are being abused needs to be addressed.
The gain of functional research needs to be
stopped, at least until it can be done at some point under
some type of control, where it actually provides a benefit
for humanity without a harm.
We need to hold people accountable that have been
responsible for doing this.
They have violated the Biological Weapons Convention
treaty. They have violated the Nuremberg Code.
They have violated the International Covenant on Civil and
Political Rights.
They have violated the American Medical Association Code of
Ethics, which may not be a criminal act, but it's the way I
thought we were kind of practicing medicine or we're
supposed to practice medicine.
There comes a time for everybody to be held accountable for
things that they do.
People make mistakes.
I'm human.
You won't have any challenges finding somebody that would
tell you that I make mistakes, okay? I know I make
mistakes. I'm my worst critic on a science and medical perspective.
Two decades worth of gain of function research
all focused on increasing the infectivity of this virus
with consequences that are very clear around the world.
We took procedures in 2020 and 2021 that make no
scientific sense.
There's no data to show that the quarantining of citizens
around the world stop this virus.
If there is, explain to me why in 2021 this virus is
endemic. It didn't stop it.
Physicians abandoned the practice of medicine for a variety
of reasons.
Some of them might have literally thought they were doing
the right thing.
Many of them did it because they were told there were no
treatments. And who told them that? Agencies out of the
federal government.
The federal government run by Fauci and Collins and other
people. Those agencies don't practice medicine.
You don't call them when you go to the hospital.
Your physician practices medicine.
That's the person you see that takes care of you.
We have interfered with the practice of medicine.
We have interfered with physicians feeling like they could
practice medicine. For the physicians who haven't bothered
to actually measure treatment outcomes but are espousing a
number of drugs.
I encourage them to actually get the quantified meausre data
to see whether they work or they don't work.
But at least they're trying something which is kind of what
we used to always do before we figured it out.
I was there when HIV hit the scenes.
We didn't know what we were doing, so we worked.
We winged it.
We treated symptoms.
They were short of breath.
We gave them breathing treatments.
2019, we quit giving breathing treatments to people short
of breath even if they were wheezing because, well, there
was no treatment, right?
All the things that we did in science and medicine
was throwing out the windows.
We locked on a society.
We put fear in everybody's heart.
We told people to quit believing people who might tell you
something different.
We quit challenging the scientific paradigm.
In science, we're always debating anybody who thinks that physicians
and scientists are just this jolly group of people that are
constantly agreeing with each other.
No scientific debate is constantly had.
Physicians frequently will talk amongst ourselves and debate
what should or shouldn't be done.
But that's a free exchange of ideas that hasn't been done.
Texas Medical Association health authorities, the governor,
the attorney general all of the people should be looking at
why this happened to make sure that Texans are taken care
of and other people in the country have an opportunity to follow.
It needs to be holding accountable to people that
caused this chaos, this mayhem to begin with and stopping
it from occurring again.
Follow truth and plain sight, bringing truth to light in
unbiased, nonpartisan factually, founded reporting
worldwide.